<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>geodesy on </title>
    <link>https://jjle.github.io/tags/geodesy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in geodesy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jjle.github.io/tags/geodesy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Land Surface Changes, Ground Deformation, and Seismicity</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/deformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/project/deformation/</guid>
      <description>We study surface changes, ground deformation, and seismicity in various settings. We primarily use remote-sensing techniques, e.g., multi-temporal Interferometric Synthetic Aperture Radar (InSAR) and GPS, and other auxiliary datasets to characterize robust ground deformation history in regions under the influences of tectonics (e.g., fault-zone deformation), surficial processes (e.g., soil moisture), and/or anthropogenic activities (e.g., agriculture and energy production).
Our focus is on the connections between surface observations and subsurface processes, including the existence or absence of seismicity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fault Zone Mechanics and Earthquake Physics</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/project/earthquake/</guid>
      <description>My interests under this broad topic include dynamic earthquake ruptures, interactions between seismic and aseismic processes, observations from geodesy, seismology, and geology, laboratory-based constitutive laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration of Seismic-Geodetic Observations</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/backup-material/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/backup-material/data/</guid>
      <description>I am particularly interested in exploring the wide spetrum of dynamic Earth processes by intergrating seismological and geodetic observations. These efforts include imaging space-time patterns of fault slip during and after earthquakes (strong motion, GPS, tide gauges, and tsunami waveforms), inferring frequency-dependent signals during the potential activation of splay faulting (seismic records and tsunami waveforms), and, more recently, imaging the continuous transition from earthquake arrest to postseismic fault slip (strong motion records, high-rate GPS, and daily GPS).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>