<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jjle.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ground Deformation and Seismicity</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/deformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/project/deformation/</guid>
      <description>In this ongoing project, I examine ground displacement histories with Interferometric Synthetic Aperture Radar (InSAR) in areas with pronounced levels of anthropogenic activity, with a focus on correlations between the rate and depth of mass change vs. the existence or non-existence of changes in seismicity rates or deformation. The overarching goal is to improve our understanding of when anthropogenic earthquakes are or are not triggered, and what that tells us about the average state and heterogeneity of stress in the shallow crust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake and Fault Zone Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/project/earthquake/</guid>
      <description>My interests under this broad topic include dynamic earthquake ruptures, interactions between seismic and aseismic processes, observations from geodesy, seismology, and geology, laboratory-based constitutive laws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computational Geophysics</title>
      <link>https://jjle.github.io/project/computation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjle.github.io/project/computation/</guid>
      <description>Extracting important and relevant physics from data and developing models with predictive power will be a significant task in the future of Earth sciences. Many of my observation-oriented projects share the theme of utilizing a probabilistic inference framework (analytical and numerical Bayesian approaches) with an emphasis on characterizing uncertainty in data and modeling, and propagating that uncertainty to inferred/predicted parameters. The other part of my research involves developing computational models with sophisticated physics and predictive powers to understand earthquakes, tsunamis, or slow slip.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>